So scared of breaking it
害怕我们之间出现问题
But you won't let it bend
而你却不想重复以前的尴尬
And I wrote two hundred letters
我写了两百封 解释为什么
I won't ever send
但却一封也没寄出去
Somehow it is cut so much  Deeper then they seem
感觉到不幸如同头上剑
You'd rather cover up I'd rather let them be
你再怎么掩饰 但米已成炊
So let me be And I'll set you free
那就随便 我还你自由吧
I am in misery There ain't no other Who can comfort me
经历过非人痛苦 谁能给我一点安慰啊
Why won't you answer me? Your silence is slowly killing me
干嘛不直接点 这就像慢性毒药慢慢折磨死我
Girl you really got me bad You really got me bad
你真真伤害我 比纳米小的自尊心
I'm gonna get you back Gonna get you back
我发誓要把你战胜
Your salty skin and how It mixes in with mine
你的痛苦跟我比小巫见大巫
The way it feels to be Completely intertwined
紧紧深陷 纠葛难以摆脱
It's not that I didn't care It's that I didn't know
不是我不在乎 是我从没有这样想过
It's not what I didn't feel, It's what I didn't show
So let me be And I'll set you free
那就随便 我还你自由吧
I am in misery There ain't no other
经历过非人痛苦
Who can comfort me
谁能给我一点安慰啊
Why won't you answer me?
干嘛不直接点
Your silence is slowly killing me
这就像慢性毒药慢慢折磨死我
Girl you really got me bad  You really got me bad
你真真伤害我 比纳米小的自尊心
I'm gonna get you back Gonna get you back
我发誓要把你战胜
Say your faith is shaken You may be mistaken
你说你可能只是一时糊涂
You keep me wide awake and
不是没有机会和你在一起
Waiting for the sun
我就知道
I'm desperate and confu sed
我挺而走险
So far away from you
糊里糊涂远离你
I'm getting here
算了 我要回到你身边
Don't care where I have to go
你别管我做什么事
Why do you do what you do to me, yeah
为什么 为什么你还要折磨我
Why won't you answer me, answer me yeah
干嘛不直接点
Why do you do what you do to me yeah
为什么 为什么你还要折磨我
Why won't you answer me, answer me yeah
干嘛不直接点
I am in misery There ain't no other
经历过非人痛苦
Who can comfort me
谁能给我一点安慰啊
Why won't you answer me?
干嘛不直接点
Your silence is slowly killing me
这就像慢性毒药慢慢折磨死我
Girl you really got me bad You really got me bad
你真真伤害我 比纳米小的自尊心
I'm gonna get you back Gonna get you back
我发誓要把你战胜
Girl you really got me bad You really got me bad
你真真伤害我 比纳米小的自尊心
I'm gonna get you back Gonna get you back
我发誓要把你战胜
Girl you really got me bad You really got me bad
你真真伤害我 比纳米小的自尊心
I'm gonna get you back Gonna get you back
我发誓要把你战胜